[roaring]
[groans]
-[thuds]
-[gasps]
[growling]
♪
[groans]
[YOO JINHO] Um, Boss?
Wanna introduce us?
[SUNG JINWOO] Oh, right.
I guess you've never
seen them before, huh?
They're a part
of one of my skills.
I didn't know
that was even possible.
So they're, like, your minions?
[SUNG JINWOO]
It's kinda hard to explain,
but yup, something like that.
[roaring]
-Huh.
-[snaps]
♪
-[hammers]
-[crackling]
[hammering]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[groans]
-[YOO JINHO] Please, Boss.
-Hm?
Let me collect
some essence stones.
Otherwise, I'm useless here.
Huh?
For me?
-Thank you so much!
-[chuckles]
Huh?
♪
[water drips]
[JAMES] Stay away!
[gasps]
Oh, Christ!
Hmm.
Hey.
Could you not scream like that?
Everything's fine.
Your friends are unconscious,
not dead.
-[James screams]
-Can't blame you, though.
I'm sure I look
more like a beast
than a person right now, huh?
[chuckles]
Listen.
♪
I'll talk slowly.
I'm human, too. Just lost.
[chuckles]
[sizzling]
-[glasses clink]
-[YOO JINHO] Bottoms up!
[gulping]
[exhales]
[exhales loudly]
That's nineteen raids cleared,
as per our deal.
Yeah, and thanks to you
we pulled it off
without too much trouble.
What you got next?
Let's see, first is
passing the written exam,
and getting
my guild master's license.
After that,
I'll start negotiating
with my dad.
-Huh?
-Makes sense.
[YOO JINHO]
What about you?
Got any big plans?
[sizzling]
I'll probably be
out of contact for a while.
Got some traveling
I need to do.
Hm? Dude.
-Hmm.
-[SUNG JINWOO] You okay?
[gulps]
[exhales loudly]
[YOO JINHO] Boss. If it's
a pain to put up with me,
you can just
come out and say it.
And...I promise that
I won't bother you anymore.
[chuckles]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Are you drunk already?
[YOO JINHO] Truth is.
There's a good decade
between me and my brother,
and I don't think
he likes me very much.
He's never once shown me any
sort of brotherly affection.
On the other hand,
you not only saved my life,
but kept helping me afterward.
So, y'know.
Sometimes I think
it would be better...
if you were my older brother.
[sizzling]
[exhales]
[gulps]
[glass thuds]
-[liquid trickling]
-[YOO JINHO] Huh?
[bottle thuds]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Then you're in luck,
-'cause from now on...
-[glass clinks]
I'll consider you my friend,
and my younger brother.
[shudders]
Huh.
We're brothers?
[sniffles]
[gulps]
[exhales]
Go on.
Eat as much as you want.
I'll grill you up a ton!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Wha... no, no, no, no,
you don't have to do that.
[YOO JINHO]
Want me to add lemon juice?
[SUNG JINWOO]
No! [chuckles]
You're drunk drunk, huh?
[YOO JINHO]
I've never been more sober!
[both laugh]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Uh-huh, sure buddy.
♪
[MALE DEPUTY CHIEF 15A]
Have we confirmed his origin?
[MALE OFFICER 15A]
He claims to be a hunter
from another country.
According to him,
he only just escaped the gate
he'd been trapped in
for the last ten years.
Seems the exit he took
spit him out of a gate
in the US.
[MALE DEPUTY CHIEF 15A]
Well, that's quite a story.
Anything else?
[MALE OFFICER 15A]
Some of the things he's said
aren't adding up,
so we're consulting
with a hunter
from his home country.
We can't rule out
the possibility
that he's a beast.
[MALE DEPUTY CHIEF 15A]
And if that's the case?
[MALE OFFICER 15A]
Don't worry, sir.
The hunter we've requested
assistance from
is an S-ranked
ex-pat living in DC.
[MALE DEPUTY CHIEF 15A]
Mister Hwang, huh?
[MALE OFFICER 15A]
Mhm. As soon as he arrives,
we'll start the interrogation.
[scoffs]
The sooner, the better.
Has this guy given us
any name to call him?
He has, but it didn't show
in our databases.
Name's Il-hwan Sung,
or so he says.
♪
[clattering]
[SUNG JINWOO]
I'll be gone for about a week.
First it's work
and now you're off traveling?
Well, someone's been
busy lately.
[SUNG JINWOO] Huh,
just a lot to do, that's all.
So, who's the lucky lady, then?
[Sung Jinwoo groans]
[exhales]
[door opens]
Like I told you, a friend.
You know you can just bring her
here sometime, right?
-Hm.
-[door shuts]
[fire roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO]
I was around level 20
when I fought the Cerberus.
Since then,
I've gotten a lot stronger.
[key clicks]
[SUNG JINWOO] My level's now
three times higher.
I should be able to handle
what's behind this door.
[key clicks]
[electricity crackling]
[door slides open]
♪
Let's see what
we're working with here.
-Hm.
-[door creaks]
[door shuts]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] Hm? A quest?
"The castle is
swarming with demons.
You will receive
a special reward
for defeating them
and collecting their souls."
In order to clear the quest,
I need to collect
ten thousand souls?
There's that many in here?
[fire crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO] Whatever.
I haven't lost sight
of my real objective.
[demons laughing]
[SUNG JINWOO] Whether it's
ten thousand or ten million...
I'll kill them all.
[demons laughing]
[birds chirping]
[YOO MYUNGHAN] You wish to take
over the guild, is that it?
Yes.
[YOO MYUNGHAN] Hmm.
And you're asking this,
knowing full well
that Jinsung's already
working on it?
[YOO JINHO] Well, I think his
plan to bring in an outsider
to run the guild is too risky.
Respectfully, sir,
I would be a be a be--
Huh.
[YOO MYUNGHAN] This hunter
you've been working with.
Jinwoo Sung.
Present at the double dungeon,
also the raid that wiped out
Dongsuk Hwang's team,
and that murderous incident
with the Surveillance Team
hunter.
It's incredible
how he's managed
to survive all that.
[exhales]
He's participated
in every single one
of your raids, correct?
Uh...
Not only that,
but during the red gate
incident from the other day.
It was apparently Hunter Sung
who led the survivors
to safety.
Uh... Huh.
[liquid trickling]
I assume you were
only able to earn
that guild master's license
by borrowing his strength,
yet you still
want to be guild leader?
[birds chirping]
-[thuds]
-[YOO JINHO] You're right.
[birds chirping]
But even so...
the one running
the Yoojin Guild should be me.
[birds chirping]
As things stand now,
Jinsung's plan--
Very well,
we'll try things your way.
Wha...?
Under one condition.
Hm.
[exhales]
After what happened
with the red gate,
I've heard rumors
that the White Tiger Guild
has been looking
to scout Hunter Sung.
But...
I want you to convince him
to join up with us instead.
Can you do that?
Hmm.
Yes, sir!
-[chuckles softly]
-[water splashing]
[YOO MYUNGHAN]
Don't disappoint me.
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
A literal mountain of demons,
and I can't extract
any of them.
What a waste.
♪
Hm.
[fire crackling]
[paper rustles]
An entry permit.
Looks like it's time to head up
to the second floor.
Hmm...guess I know
how I'm getting there.
This dungeon is
surprisingly big.
Who'd've thought
there'd be a whole city
inside of a building.
Though all this walking is
getting pretty annoying.
♪
[roars]
[thuds]
You're about to save me
a lot of time and effort.
You're a big boy.
All right, then.
Let's get moving.
[Tank growls]
[Jinwoo sighs]
What a pain in the a...
[gasps]
[growls]
[roars]
[thuds]
[Tank roars]
[chuckles]
Nice one.
♪
I think I'll call you "Tank".
Sound good?
[water splashing]
[machine whirring]
[water splashes]
[exhales]
[FEMALE HUNTER 15A] No!
Miss Hae-in is here?
[FEMALE HUNTER 15B]
Feels lucky just seeing her.
[FEMALE HUNTER 15A]
And she always looks amazing!
[FEMALE HUNTER 15B]
Mhm, always!
[CHA HAE-IN]
I don't get it.
Why would we keep the reports
of the flying ants
confidential?
People deserve the truth.
It's on Association orders.
They say it would cause a panic
if we make the intel public
at this stage.
-[CHA HAE-IN] But sir!
-It'll be fine.
For the time being, let's focus
on gaining strength.
As the largest domestic guild,
doing so will help us
execute our duties and expand.
[thuds]
[SUNG JINWOO]
I thought this was gonna be
an S-Rank dungeon
when I got the key,
but these guys
weren't that tough.
More like the upper end
of B-Rank.
They come in droves,
and they get fiercer
the higher up I go.
I'm making
decent progress though,
by only killing the demons
I need to, to advance.
[thuds]
[SUNG JINWOO] A good strategy.
Because if the Demon's Castle
is laid out
like the original tower,
there are a hundred floors
to get through.
That's a ton of XP,
so how strong will I be
once I reach the top?
-[thuds]
-[slurps]
[SUNG JINWOO] My supplies
won't last forever,
and Jinah thinks
I'll be back in a week.
This fight...
is really
a battle against time.
♪
[chomps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Let's see how far I can get.
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] A red one.
[rustling]
[PARK HEEJIN] Of course
Hunter Sung would be out.
[AHN SANGMIN] Well, at least
his sister was home.
Thanks to her, we know
he's off on some kind of trip.
Meaning, we came all this way
for nothing, then.
Meh. We're gathering intel,
which is crucial
since he quit doing raids.
He can't have
left the country, though.
The Association has been
keeping tabs on him,
and when they lost him,
he was in the middle of a city.
Wait. You knew all of that
about him already?
[chuckles]
I have to, it's my job.
[sighs]
But, man.
I wish I knew where he was.
Think I'll take on
that boss there myself.
You guys, you know what to do.
[roaring]
[fire roaring]
[explosion]
[slashing]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] With a good chunk
of points in my intellect now,
I can summon more soldiers,
and have more magical power
to maintain them,
which makes fighting easier.
But, I mean,
can it be called a fight
if your opponent
doesn't even move?
If it's not gonna attack,
I guess I'll...
[gasps]
[roars]
Do you think
that's gonna work on me?
[crashes]
[gasps]
I did that with a single punch?
My strength stat's
pretty broken.
[growls]
[roars]
This happened
with the Cerberus, too!
[roars]
[growls]
Iron!
[roars]
[grunts]
[clangs]
-[thumping]
-[grunting]
[SUNG JINWOO]
It is not slowing down!
How's something
that big so fast?
But, I just need to wait
for an opening.
[growls]
-Now!
-[thumping]
[thuds]
[grunts]
I got you!
[growls]
[gasps]
[smacks]
[thuds]
[Sung Jinwoo grunts]
It's smart.
Predicts my moves
and everything.
It'd seem invulnerable,
if not for those
beady little eyes.
[thuds]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] Gotta stop
this thing from zipping around.
But how?
That'll work!
[thuds]
♪
[growls]
[roars]
[crashes]
[grunts]
Should've been
watching your step there.
[growls]
[grunts]
[groans]
[thuds]
[rocks thudding]
♪
[explosion]
[HWANG DONGSOO] They say
you're a magic beast
that can talk.
[thuds]
Yeah, and I keep
telling them I'm no beast.
If what you're after is proof,
I have zero issues whatsoever
doing a DNA test.
Can it, you creep.
If I don't ask a question,
then you stay silent.
I'm pissed off as it is,
what with all of my fun
put on hold.
-[chair clatters]
-I swear.
They even went
and wrote a bunch
of dumb paperwork for you.
[SUNG IL-HWAN]
Hey, let me ask something.
Can it, I said.
[SUNG IL-HWAN]
How much has humanity
learned about the gates
and magic beasts?
What?
Since gates and beasts
first appeared,
how much have you learned?
What are you getting at?
Freak show.
[SUNG IL-HWAN] The dungeons,
the gates, the beasts.
They're just
the tip of the iceberg.
The power to bring forth
the ultimate catastrophe
has awakened.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
What catastrophe?
[SUNG IL-HWAN]
The ultimate one.
Not much else I can say.
[scoffs]
So?
My primary goal
is to prevent it
from coming to pass.
Whatever you are,
it's not a conversationalist.
And even if
this threat did exist,
every corner of the world's
got hunters
who'd be willing to take it on.
[SUNG IL-HWAN]
Numbers won't help.
Most will either be devoured.
Or enslaved
and used against us.
You seem fairly strong
yourself, but...
[DONGSOO]
But what?
[scoffs]
Not every day you see
a magic beast
with a name of his own.
And look at that.
A wife and kids, too?
Huh.
[chuckles]
Do you remember
your son's name?
Jinwoo.
Did that trigger you somehow?
[pad clatters]
[HWANG DONGSOO] I'm the one
asking questions, not you.
You'll answer that.
[HWANG DONGSOO]
My answer's "screw you".
But I'll also fill you in
on a little secret.
Your son is dead.
You got anything to say,
tell him in the next life
once you eat it, too!
[growls]
[flags fluttering]
[slashing]
[rumbling]
[SUNG JINWOO] Come on.
It's almost too easy.
[chuckles]
Sorry,
but did my boys
give you trouble?
Weren't expecting it
to go this way, huh?
I'd wonder
if the undead feel fear, but...
Who cares?
[slashing]
[thuds]
[squelching]
♪
[siren wailing]
[MALE FIREFIGHTER 15A]
Over here!
[MALE FIREFIGHTER 15B]
Move! Move!
[MALE OFFICER 15A] I've heard
that fights between S-Ranks
can affect entire landscapes,
laying waste
to everything around them.
Damn, maybe we were
fortunate.
Could've been much worse,
I agree.
Would've been,
but it was over so fast.
Before they could do
any more damage,
Mister Hwang
lost almost instantly.
♪
[Sung Jinwoo sighs]
That was
the last of my rations.
I guess I'm done for now.
The seventy-fifth floor.
Twenty-five floors left, maybe.
Which is still
a long way to go.
Well, can't be mad
at the gains.
Like the earring I got
from the giant
on the fiftieth floor.
And the necklace
from the skeleton just now.
They're useful enough
on their own,
but the set bonus
is the cherry on top.
And that empty space tells me
there's one more boss
with some accessory to win.
-[thuds]
-[SUNG JINWOO] Then there's
this Sphere of Avarice.
It doesn't affect
my stats directly, but...
I don't have to be the one
who uses it.
In the hands of my mages,
it'll double their firepower.
And, of course,
getting the cursed
random loot box
as a quest reward
was a win, too.
I was worried I'd never
get another chance at it.
Oh wow, another key.
I am so shocked.
Really? Not gonna tell me
where or when to use it?
[inhales]
Well, not like I was really
after the key anyway.
On the fiftieth floor,
I got a World-Tree Fragment
from Avaricious Vulcan.
And on the seventy-fifth,
I got Echo-Forest Spring Water
by defeating Metus,
the Guide of Souls.
The Elixir of Life only needs
three ingredients,
and I have two of them.
One more.
One more and I save Mom.
When I come back,
it's on.
[rumbling]
♪